http://hitslog.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
We will NOT provide your email address to any advertisers. We will only contact you for problems with your counter or your account.
HitsLog service collects visitor information like browser, domain names, referring URLs, IP addresses, etc. This information used purely for statistical purposes and is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Visitors will be anonymous. We will not sell, give or share your personal information with anyone.
Our web site statistics service use cookies to track visitors on sites using the HitsLog service. This cookie is used only to collect broad statistical information and to remember your login information so you do not have to type it in everytime you want to access your statistics.
HitsLog.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our News page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Recommended
Graphic converter  Free Web Counter
Enter your search terms
Submit search form
Ecommerce Development  |
Internet Monitoring Software  |
SEO
Copyright 2004-2009 © HitsLog, All rights reserved. Site Map | Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions
